[{"answer": "The Ink", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"I", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " ..Alright", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I gotta get to the airport", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He really did an amazing job, look! He uncoagulated the top of the dishwashing liquid.  He cleaned out the bottom of the little egg cups. Come here, look at this.  He cleaned the little on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "..Why did I think there was a Rubber Man? There's Elastic Man and Plastic Man", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What statue", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You have a statue? I never saw a statue", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Are you sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Ninet", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I never saw the statue", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What are you talking about", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, I had a statue in my house. You were in my house", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What am I saying", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, I.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I can't believe what I'm hearing", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I can't believe what I'm hearing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " A pawn shop", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Did you call me a wuss", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I said luss.. I'm at a luss.", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Maybe you think we're in cahoots", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes, that's all, a coincidence", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, no.. but it is quite a coincidence", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "A big coincidence", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes, that's all, a coincidence", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Not a big coincidence. A coincidence", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "A big coincidence", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, that's a big coincidence", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Not a big coincidence. A coincidence", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That's what a coincidence is! There are no small coincidences and big coincidences", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No, that's a big coincidence", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, there are degrees of coincidences", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "That's what a coincidence is! There are no small coincidences and big coincidences", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Statue.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, there are only coincidences! ..Ask anyone!  Are there big coincidences and small coincidences, or just coincidences?  ..Well?! Well?!..", "qsentId": 36}]